// Questions content
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Who was the lead actor in Interstellar?",
        answer: "Matthew McConaughey",
        options: [
            "Matt Damonn",
            "Matthew McConaughey",
            "Anne Hathaway",
            "Michael Caine"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What movie did Tom Hanks score his first Academy Award nomination?",
        answer: "Big",
        options: [
            "Forrest Gump",
            "Cast Away",
            "Big",
            "Saving Private Ryan",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "In the Matrix, what was the colour of the pill Neo took?",
        answer: "Red",
        options: [
            "Red",
            "Blue",
            "Green",
            "Yellow",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the highest-grossing R-rated movie of all time?",
        answer: "Joker",
        options: [
            "Deadpool",
            "Joker",
            "Logan",
            "None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question : "In which movie did Tom Cruise break his ankle while filming?",
        answer: "Mission Impossible: Fallout",
        options: [
            "Top Gun",
            "Jack Reacher",
            "Mission Impossible: Fallout",
            "Oblivion",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question : "In which movie did Keanu Reeves learn Judo, Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu, marksmanship and driving, and performed about 95% of the fight scenes himself?",
        answer: "John Wick: Chapter 2",
        options: [
            "The Matrix",
            "John Wick: Chapter 2",
            "Bill & Ted's Excellent Adventure",
            "The SpongeBob Movie: Sponge on the Run",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question : "What's the last word in this famous Toy Story quote: 'To infinity and ____!'",
        answer: "' Beyond! '",
        options: [
            "' Forever! '",
            "' To Tommorow! '",
            "' Beyond! '",
            "' More! '",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question : "Which is the First US film to Feature a toilet flushing?",
        answer: "Psycho",
        options: [
            "Psycho",
            "Die Hard",
            "Rush Hour",
            "Toy Story",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question : "In which movie did Leonardo DiCaprio have to devour a raw slab of bison's liver, despite being a vegetarian?",
        answer: "The Revenant",
        options: [
            "Django unchained",
            "The Revenant",
            "The Titanic",
            "None of the above.",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question : "Which Disney movie features the 'You Can Fly' song?",
        answer: "Peter Pan",
        options: [
            "Pirates of the Caribbean",
            "The Lion King",
            "Frozen",
            "Peter Pan",
        ]
    }
];